fxcharts.com.au 2012-10-19

# Privacy Policy | FX Charts: Forex Analysis | Daily Forex Report | Weekly Forex Report | Forex Outlook

**FX Charts Respects Each Individual’s Right to Privacy.** We realise how important it is for us to safeguard any personal information that may reveal your identity or account information, whether you are a client or a visitor to our Web site’s public domain. **Your Privacy is Our Priority** FX Charts P/L is committed to its privacy obligations under the National Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988. This privacy policy describes how we handle and protect personal information we collect about individuals who choose to apply for or receive our services. **How We Collect Personal Information** When you apply to register to receive the FX Charts Daily newsletter, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such processing your requests, informing you intraday market moves that may possibly of interest to you, and providing client service. The personal information we collect about you will be through a registration process that you will be required to complete, should you choose to receive the service. Once you have registered, you will be allocated a password in order to login to the private area of the website. **What kind of Information do we collect?** We collect a limited amount of information about our members, so that we can provide a site that is interesting, current and useful to our readers. Should you choose to register to receive the daily output from fxcharts.com.au you will be required to give your name and email address only. **Will we disclose the information?** FX Charts shares your concern about the protection of your personal information online. FX Charts acts as a registered Introducing broker to AxiCorp Financial Services P/L and will disclose your personal information only to the extent necessary that they can see who is following the site. There is no compunction to open a trading account with them. Other than that, we will not disclose any personal information to any third parties, except when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, to protect other users of FX Charts or to respond to an emergency. **What do we do with the information?** FX Charts uses information obtained from its users to enhance their experience of the site.  Tracking information is used to create aggregate reports on user demographics and site traffic patterns. This data will be passed on to AxiCorp Financial Services, but to no other third party. **Security Disclaimer:** FX Charts uses reasonable security methods to protect the data that resides on our servers. However, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our servers, nor can we guarantee that information that users supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.
